A Guide to the Philip S. Hench Walter Reed Yellow Fever Collection 1806-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- HENRY ROSE CARTER TO HIS FAMILY N.D., *ALS (Box-folder 013-013)
  FRAGMENTS
- DIFFERENTIATION BETWEEN YELLOW FEVER AND MALARIA N.D., TMs (Box-folder 013-014)
- ORDINANCE FOR THE CONTROL OF MOSQUITO PRODUCTION N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 013-015)
- NEWSPAPER FRAGMENT RE HENRY ROSE CARTER'S INCUBATION THEORY N.D., NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 013-016)
- MEMORANDUM AND BRIEF BIOGRAPHICAL SKETCH OF HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs, TMs (Box-folder 013-017)
- CUBAN STAMPS N.D., STAMPS (Box-folder 013-018)
- FRAGMENTS OF NOTES AND COMMENTS ON YELLOW FEVER AND TROPICAL DISEASE BY HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 013-019)
- FRAGMENT OF REPORT ON TROPICAL DISEASE BY HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 013-020)
- FRAGMENT OF NOTES BY HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs/TMs (Box-folder 013-021)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS N.D., TMs, TMs (CC) (2) (Box-folder 013-022)
- BIBLIOGRAPHY OF ARTICLES ON YELLOW FEVER AND MALARIA BY HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., TMs, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 013-023)
- HENRY ROSE CARTER, MISCELLANEOUS NOTES AND MEMORANDA N.D. (Box-folder 013-024)
- NOTES ON YELLOW FEVER, MALARIA, AND OTHER TROPICAL DISEASES BY HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., *AMs, TMs (Box-folder 013-025)
- NOTES FROM MALARIA SURVEYS N.D., TMs (Box-folder 013-026)
- MEMORANDUM OF PHYSICAL SURVEY OF PORTIONS OF THE SITE TO BE COVERED BY THE WATER IMPOUNDED AT BADIN, N.C. N.D., TMsS (CC) (Box-folder 013-027)
- PIONEERING IN PANAMA N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 013-028)
  EXCERPTS FROM PANAMA DIARY OF LAURA ARMISTEAD CARTER
- POEMS N.D., TMs (Box-folder 013-029)
- THE LINE OF INVESTIGATION WHICH WAS PROPOSED FOR MR. DUNN BY HENRY HANSON N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 013-030)
- CORRESPONDENCE OF HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., 14 ITEMS (Box-folder 013-031)
- CASE HISTORY AND POST-MORTEM, MAKURDI, NIGERIA [RECORDED BY THE INTERNATIONAL HEALTH DIVISION, ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION] N.D., 1 ITEM (Box-folder 013-032)
- CARTER PAPERS - MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE, CATALOGUING ERRORS 1922-1926, 3 ITEMs (Box-folder 013-033)
- TELEGRAM FROM H. A. BONZI TO HENRY ROSE CARTER [1921]/02/28, TL (Box-folder 013-034)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTEBOOKS, CARD FILES, MAP OF HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs (8), MAP (Box-folder 014-001)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTEBOOKS, MAP OF HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs (6), MAP (Box-folder 014-002)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES OF HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 014-003)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES OF HENRY ROSE CARTER N.D., AMs (Box-folder 014-004)
- REVIEW OF WILLIAM CRAWFORD GORGAS: HIS LIFE AND WORK BY MARIE D. GORGAS AND BURTON J. HENDRICK 1924, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-001)
- THE TREATMENT OF ORIENTAL SORE BY ALDO CASTELLANI 1924, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-002)
- DISCUSSION BY DR. THOMPSON OF BLACK WATER FEVER BY J.W.W. STEPHENS 1925, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-003)
- COMMENT BY DR. HENRY ROSE CARTER ON RELATION OF LEPTOSPIRA ICTEROIDES TO YELLOW FEVER 1924, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-004)
- OBSERVATIONS DURING THE YELLOW FEVER EPIDEMIC, WHICH EXISTED FROM DECEMBER 1908 TO FEBRUARY 1909 IN PARAMARIBO BY P.C. FLU 1924, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-005)
- DISCUSSIONS OF PAPERS ON HOOK WORK, AMERICAN ANOPHELINE MOSQUITOES, AND MALARIA CARRIERS 1924, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-006)
- FAME OF REED AND GORGAS BY JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1924, TMs (CC) (3) (Box-folder 015-007)
- NOTES ON YELLOW FEVER IN BRITISH GUIANA BY J. RODWAY 1924, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-008)
- SHORT BIOGRAPHICAL SKETCHES OF HENRY ROSE CARTER 1924, TMs, CLIPPING (Box-folder 015-009)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSPAPER AND MAGAZINE CLIPPINGS 1924, *NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (Box-folder 015-010)
- MISCELLAENOUS UNTITLED PAPERS 1924, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 015-011)
- MISCELLAENOUS NOTEBOOKS 1924, AMs (5) (Box-folder 015-012)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1924/ca., AMs (Box-folder 015-013)
- ON THE YELLOW MALIGNANT FEVER 1806/06/21, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 016-001)
  THE NEW-YORK HERALD
- THE NEW YORK HERALD 1853/08/18, NEWSPAPER (Box-folder 016-002)
  CONTAINS ARTICLE ON YELLOW FEVER IN NEW ORLEANS WITH A NOTE BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH
- INVENTORY AND INSPECTION REPORT OF AMBULANCES UNDER SUPERVISION OF M.R. BALDWIN 1863/03/05, PRINTED FORM WITH AA (Box-folder 016-003)
- THE HISTORY OF A ROSE BY EMILY B. LAWRENCE 1867, AMs (Box-folder 016-004)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1874/07/18, ALS (Box-folder 016-005)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1874/08/12, ALS (Box-folder 016-006)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1874/09/17, ALS (Box-folder 016-007)
  16 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1874/09/28, AN (Box-folder 016-008)
  1 PAGE WITH ENVELOPE REQUESTS PERMISSION TO CALL
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1874/10/28, ALS (Box-folder 016-009)
  12 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1974/11/23, ALS (Box-folder 016-010)
- MATERIALS RELATING TO WALTER REED'S APPEARANCE BEFORE ARMY EXAMINATION BOARD 1874, AMs (P) (Box-folder 016-011)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/01/09, ALS (Box-folder 016-012)
  13 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/01/20, ALS (Box-folder 016-013)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/02/03, ALS (Box-folder 016-014)
  7 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE
- WALTER REED - EXAMINATIONS FOR QUALIFICATION AS ARMY SURGEON 1875/02/08, AMs (P) (Box-folder 016-015)
- AUTOBIOGRAPHY OF WALTER REED 1875/02/08, AMs (P) (Box-folder 016-016)
- AUTOBIOGRAPHY OF WALTER REED 1875/02/08, AMs (P) (Box-folder 016-017)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/03/04, ALS (Box-folder 016-018)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/03/24, ALS (Box-folder 016-019)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/03/ca., ALS (Box-folder 016-020)
  3 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE (FRAGMENT)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/04/08, ALS (Box-folder 016-021)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/05/12, AN (Box-folder 016-022)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/05/17, ALS (Box-folder 016-023)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/05/17, ALS (Box-folder 016-024)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/05/19, ALS (Box-folder 016-025)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/05/27, ALS (Box-folder 016-026)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/06/01, ALS (Box-folder 016-027)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/06/06, ALS (Box-folder 016-028)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/06/11, ALS (Box-folder 016-029)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/06/15, ALS (Box-folder 016-030)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/06/17, ALS (Box-folder 016-031)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/06/21, ALS (Box-folder 016-032)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/07/01, ALS (Box-folder 016-033)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/07/23, ALS (Box-folder 016-034)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/07/23, ALS (Box-folder 016-035)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/07/25, ALS (Box-folder 016-036)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/07/27, ALS (Box-folder 016-037)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/07/29, ALS (Box-folder 016-038)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/01, ALS (Box-folder 016-039)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/05, ALS (Box-folder 016-040)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/08, ALS (Box-folder 016-041)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/12, ALS (Box-folder 016-042)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/16, ALS (Box-folder 016-043)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/19, ALS (Box-folder 016-044)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/19-23, ALS (Box-folder 016-045)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/27, ALS (Box-folder 016-046)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/08/30, ALS (Box-folder 016-047)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/09/03, ALS (Box-folder 016-048)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/09/06, ALS (Box-folder 016-049)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/09/09, ALS (Box-folder 016-050)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/09/20, ALS (Box-folder 016-051)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/09/23, ALS (Box-folder 016-052)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/09/27, ALS (Box-folder 016-053)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875.09/29, ALS (Box-folder 016-054)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/10/04, ALS (Box-folder 016-055)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/10/18, ALS (Box-folder 016-056)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/10/21, ALS (Box-folder 016-057)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/10/25, ALS (Box-folder 016-058)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/10/29, ALS (Box-folder 016-059)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/10/31, ALS (Box-folder 016-060)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/11/11, ALS (Box-folder 016-061)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/11/15, ALS (Box-folder 016-062)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/11/17, ALS (Box-folder 016-063)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/11/22, ALS (Box-folder 016-064)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/11/29, ALS (Box-folder 016-065)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/09, ALS (Box-folder 016-066)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/13, ALS (Box-folder 016-067)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/13, ALS (Box-folder 016-068)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/14, ALS (Box-folder 016-069)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/16, ALS (Box-folder 016-070)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/20, ALS (Box-folder 016-071)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/22, ALS (Box-folder 016-072)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/12/29, ALS (Box-folder 016-073)
- WALTER REED - CERTIFICATION OF PASSING OF ARMY EXAMINATIONS AND APPOINTMENT AS ASSISTANT SURGEON 1875, AMs (P) (Box-folder 016-074)
- EMPTY ENVELOPES OF LETTERS FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/ca., AENVELOPES (6) (Box-folder 016-075)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1875/ca., ANS (2) (Box-folder 016-076)
  CARDS REQUESTING PERMISSION TO CALL
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/01/06, ALS (Box-folder 017-001)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/01/10, ALS (Box-folder 017-002)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/01/13, ALS (Box-folder 017-003)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/01/17, ALS (Box-folder 017-004)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/01/24, ALS (Box-folder 017-005)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/01/27, ALS (Box-folder 017-006)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/02/07, ALS (Box-folder 017-007)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/02/11, ALS (Box-folder 017-008)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/02/16, ALS (Box-folder 017-009)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1876/02/17, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-010)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/02/22, ALS (Box-folder 017-011)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/04, ALS (Box-folder 017-012)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/06, ALS (Box-folder 017-013)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/09, ALS (Box-folder 017-014)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/13, ALS (Box-folder 017-015)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/20, ALS (Box-folder 017-016)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/23, ALS (Box-folder 017-017)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/28, ALS (Box-folder 017-018)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/03/20, ALS (Box-folder 017-019)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/04/03, ALS (Box-folder 017-020)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/04/06, ALS (Box-folder 017-021)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/04/10, ALS (Box-folder 017-022)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE B. LAWRENCE 1876/04/13, ALS (Box-folder 017-023)
- INSPECTION REPORT BY WALTER REED, DEPARTMENT OF ARIZONA 1877, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-024)
- COMMENTS BY WALTER REED ABOUT LIFE IN THE WEST 1877/12/ca., TMs (Box-folder 017-025)
  FROM WALTER REED AND YELLOW FEVER BY HOWARD A. KELLY, CHAPTER II, 'FRONTIER LIFE' (1876-1889), PAGES 25-29, 32-34
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1878/01/31, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-026)
- INCIDENTS OF THE SCOURGE OF THE SOUTH 1878/09/21, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-027)
  FRANK LESLIE'S ILLUSTRATED NEWSPAPER
- QUARANTINE PRECAUTIONS AGAINST YELLOW FEVER 1878/09/21, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-028)
- PICTURES OF CITIZENS CONTRIBUTING TO VICTIMS OF YELLOW FEVER 1878/09/28, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (P) (2) (Box-folder 017-029)
- THE YELLOW FEVER VISITATION 1878/09/28, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-030)
- NEW YORK'S CONTRIBUTION TO THE SUFFERING SOUTH 1878/09/28, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-031)
- THE LESSONS OF CALAMITY 1878/10/05, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-032)
- ARTICLE AND PICTURES RE YELLOW FEVER 1878/01/11, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-033)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1879/03/17, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-034)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/04/21, ALS (Box-folder 017-035)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/04/23, ALS (Box-folder 017-036)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/04/26, APCS (Box-folder 017-037)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/04/29, APCS (Box-folder 017-038)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/04/30, APCS (Box-folder 017-039)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/05/06, ALS (Box-folder 017-040)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/05/15, ALS (Box-folder 017-041)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/05/22, ALS (Box-folder 017-042)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/05/25, ALS (Box-folder 017-043)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/05/31, ALS (Box-folder 017-044)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/06/03, ALS (Box-folder 017-045)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/06/23, ALS (Box-folder 017-046)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/07/05, ALS (Box-folder 017-047)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/07/09, ALS (Box-folder 017-048)
  14 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/07/21, ALS (Box-folder 017-049)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/08/25, ALS (Box-folder 017-050)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/09/06, ALS (Box-folder 017-051)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/09/08, ALS (Box-folder 017-052)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1879/09/29, AL (Box-folder 017-053)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1879/10/01, AL (Box-folder 017-054)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1879/10/07, AL (Box-folder 017-055)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1879/10/20, AL (Box-folder 017-056)
- ENVELOPE ADDRESSED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1897/10/20/ca., AENVELOPE (Box-folder 017-057)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/10/27, ALS (Box-folder 017-058)
  20 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE
- ENVELOPE ADDRESSED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/07/04, AENVELOPE (Box-folder 017-059)
- YELLOW FEVER IN MEMPHIS 1879/08/23, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-060)
- ENVELOPE ADDRESSED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1879/09/10/ca., AENVELOPE (Box-folder 017-061)
- MEMPHIS UNDER QUARANTINE RULE 1879/09/20, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 017-062)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/12/08, ALS (Box-folder 017-063)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/12/16, ALS (Box-folder 017-064)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/12/23, ALS (Box-folder 017-065)
  10 PAGES
- ENVELOPE ADDRESSED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1879/12/25, AENVELOPE (Box-folder 017-066)
  MISSING
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1880/01/13, ALS (Box-folder 017-067)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/01/28, ALS (Box-folder 017-068)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/02/04, ALS (Box-folder 017-069)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/02/18, ALS (Box-folder 017-070)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/02/27, ALS (Box-folder 017-071)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/04/02, ALS (Box-folder 017-072)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/06/18, ALS (Box-folder 017-073)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/07/10, ALS (Box-folder 017-074)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY MCPHERSON 1880/ca., AL (Box-folder 017-075)
  2 PAGES (FRAGMENT0
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1880, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-076)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1881/04/03, ALS (Box-folder 017-077)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1881, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-078)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1882, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-079)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1885, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-080)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1885/12/26, ALS (Box-folder 017-081)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DORSEY M. MCPHERSON 1886/04/13, ALS (Box-folder 017-082)
  2 PAGES (IN 3 PIECES)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO POST ADJUTANT 1887/05/04, AL (Box-folder 017-083)
  SANITATION REPORT
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1887, AMs (P) (Box-folder 017-084)
- ESSAY BY WILLIAM H. WELCH ON WORK OF WALTER REED AT JOHNS HOPKINS HOSPITAL 1890, AMs (Box-folder 018-001)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1890, AMs (P) (Box-folder 018-002)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1891, AMs (P) (Box-folder 018-003)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1892, AMs (P) (Box-folder 018-004)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO C.B. BYRNE 1893/03/07, ALS (Box-folder 018-005)
  5 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE CONTAINS DIRECTIONS AS TO METHOD OF STAINING TUBERCULE BACILLI
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1893/06/29, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-006)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO THEOBALD SMITH 1893/12/05, ALS (Box-folder 018-007)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1893, AMs (P), TMs (P) (Box-folder 018-008)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO DR. BORDEN 1894/03/15, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-009)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1894/06/12, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-010)
- A PRECIS OF THE UNITED STATES QUARANTINE REGULATIONS FOR DOMESTIC PORTS WITH REFERENCE TO PREVENTING THE INTRODUCTION OF YELLOW FEVER INTO THE UNITED STATES BY PRESTON H. BAILHACHE 1897/08/27/ca., REPORT (P) (Box-folder 018-011)
- ANNUAL REPORT OF MARINE HOSPITAL SERVICE: THERAPEUTIC TREATMENT OF YELLOW FEVER BY H.D. GEDDINGS 1894, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 018-012)
- HARPER'S WEEKLY 1894/04/13, MAGAZINE (Box-folder 018-013)
  RE HAVANA, CUBA
- HARPER'S WEEKLY 1895/05/11, MAGAZINE (Box-folder 018-014)
- HARPER'S WEEKLY 1895/05/25, MAGAZINE (Box-folder 018-015)
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1895, AMs (P), TMs (P) (Box-folder 018-016)
- THE CUBAN INSURRECTION 1896/05/28, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 018-017)
  LESLIE'S WEEKLY
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1896/08/22, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-018)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1896/08/01, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-019)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1896/08/10, ALS (Box-folder 018-020)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1896/11/11, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-021)
  8 PAGES
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1896, AMs (P), TMs (P) (Box-folder 018-022)
- PAGES FROM THE DIARY OF JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1897-1900, AMs (P), AMs (Box-folder 018-023)
  WITH NOTES BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1897, AMs (P) (Box-folder 018-024)
- CIRCULAR LETTER RELATING TO POST-EPIDEMIC DISINFECTION AERATION 1897, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 018-025)
- MORTALITY RATE FROM YELLOW FEVER 1897-1898, AMs, TN (Box-folder 018-026)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO STANFORD E. CHAILLE 1898/02/15, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 018-027)
- LETTER FROM ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1898/04/18, ALS (P) (2) (Box-folder 018-028)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE 1898/04/19, TLS (P) (3) (Box-folder 018-029)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1898/04/23, ALS (Box-folder 018-030)
- GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG - ORDER ASSIGNING ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE TO PATHOLOGICAL LAB OF SURGEON GENERAL'S OFFICE 1898/05/03, TLS (P) (2) (Box-folder 018-031)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1898/05/10, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-032)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1898/06/21, ALS (Box-folder 018-033)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1898/07/05, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-034)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1898/07/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 018-035)
- LETTER FROM ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1898/07/29, ALS (P) (Box-folder 018-036)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1898/07/29, TLS (P) (Box-folder 018-037)
- APPOINTMENT OF WALTER REED, VICTOR C. VAUGHAN, AND EDWARD O. SHAKESPEARE TO STUDY PREVALENCE OF TYPHOID FEVER IN MILITARY CAMPS WITHIN LIMITS OF U.S. 1898/08/18, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 018-038)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JAMES CARROLL 1898/09/09, TL (TYPESCRIPT) (Box-folder 018-039)
- ARTICLE ON AMERICAN OCCUPATION OF SANTIAGO 1898/09/17, MAGAZINE CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 018-040)
  HARPER'S WEEKLY
- LETTER FROM FITZHUGH LEE TO WALTER REED 1898/09/27, TLS (Box-folder 018-041)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO WALTER REED, EMILIE LAWRENCE REED AND BLOSSOM [EMILIE M.] REED 1898/10/23, ALS (Box-folder 018-042)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1898/10/27, TL (Box-folder 018-043)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO WALTER REED 1898/11/08, ALS (Box-folder 018-044)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO WALTER REED, EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1898/11/22, ALS (Box-folder 018-045)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1898/11/24, TLS (P) (2) (Box-folder 018-046)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO WALTER REED 1898/11/28, ALS (Box-folder 018-047)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO WALTER REED 1898/12/09, ALS (Box-folder 018-048)
- REVEREND LEMUEL S. REED, LETTER FROM ATCHESON HENCH TO PHILIP HENCH, REGISTER OF THE M. E. CHURCH SOUTH (METHODIST EPISCOPAL) [CHARLOTTESVILLE] 1898, 1948, 1865-66, REPORT (P), AD (P), ALS, AN (Box-folder 018-049)
  MINTUES OF THE 116TH SESSION OF THE VIRGINIA ANNUAL CONFERENCE OF THE METHODIST EPISCOPAL CHURCH
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1898, TMs (P), REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 018-050)
- THE JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY REGISTER 1898-99 1898, PAMPHLET (Box-folder 018-051)
  51 PAGES
- THE JOHNS HOPKINS MEDICAL SCHOOL SIXTH ANNUAL ANNOUNCEMENT 1898-99 1898, PAMPHLET (Box-folder 018-052)
  94 PAGES
- ARITCLES ON YELLOW FEVER: ITS NATURE, DIAGNOSIS, TREATMENT, AND PROPHYLAXIS, AND QUARANTINE REGULATIONS RELATING THERETO 1898, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 018-053)
  8 PAGES; WALTER WYMAN; R. D. MURRAY
- TELEGRAM FROM CHARLES LOCKHART ET. AL. TO WILLIAM MCKINLEY 1898/ca., TELEGRAM (P) (Box-folder 018-054)